http://www.dallasmuseumofart.org/privacy

Skip to main content
The Dallas Museum of Art is committed to respecting the privacy of its online guests, customers, members, donors, and friends.
This Privacy Policy governs personal information provided or obtained on DMA.org, The DMA Friends website and kiosks, ShopDMA.org, ArturosArtStories.org, DMA mobile applications, and other Dallas Museum of Art websites (collectively “Sites”). It also explains how we may collect, use, and sometimes share that information.
Information you provide
The DMA collects the information you voluntarily provide in communications and transactions with the Museum, such as your name, phone number, email address, credit card information, and any digital images or written content you upload.
We use this information only for ordinary Museum purposes, such as to respond to your inquiries, update your Friends or member profile, process transactions, and for posting of information on a Museum Site as requested by you. With your permission, we may also send you Museum-related news and information. You may opt out of Museum communications at any time.
DMA Mobile Application
When you use the DMA mobile app we may generate a unique ID for your profile. Apple iOS provides unique IDs which perform identifying functions similar to “cookies” as described below. These enable us and the user to link across multiple platforms and improve the application over time. For example, artwork a user “favorites” in the mobile application will be associated with the user’s ID.
Push notifications are the messages that mobile apps send to your mobile device. With your permission, you may receive notifications periodically to inform you of Museum-related activities. You may deactivate these at any time in your device’s settings.
Friends Program
When you sign up for the DMA Friends program, we create your Friends profile using your name, phone number, email address, and any other additional information you choose to provide. DMA Members can use their membership card to log in and link their membership and DMA Friends profiles together. Your Friends program activity is collected along with user preferences and earned badges and rewards.
This information is used for the operation of the Friends program and may become associated with your DMA profile. If you participate, your email address or phone number will be used for authentication and security. With your permission, we may also collect geolocational information associated with mobile phone use. The DMA may use a social media tool program in order to review, study, and, where permissible, re-publish publically available Museum-related social media content.
Information Security
The Dallas Museum of Art is committed to maintaining the security of your personal information. We employ commercially reasonable security measures to secure and protect the information we receive, but absolute security cannot be guaranteed.  The DMA shall not be liable for the transfer or use of any personal information resulting from loss or distribution of data, the corruption of storage media, power failures, natural phenomena, riots, acts of vandalism, sabotage or terrorism or any other event beyond the DMA’s commercially reasonable control.
We may retain and use communications with our Sites, transaction details, and identifying information (such as IP addresses) in order to maintain audit trails for security purposes. In addition, when you access and use our Sites, we may automatically record information about that activity. This includes your browser type, your operating system and device model, your device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address or other identifier, the types of information you search for and view on our Sites, locale preferences, system memory information, and your mobile carrier. If you arrived at our Sites by clicking on a link on another website, we may also take note of the web page you visited before you came to our Sites.
We use this information to improve our Sites, understand users’ preferences, and improve Museum services and programs.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data file that our Sites may transfer to your device. We may use cookies to collect information in order to study, enhance, and improve the use and capabilities of our Sites. We also use cookies to enable certain features of our Sites, and to preserve your preferences and customize your experience when you visit and return to our Sites. Most browsers provide controls whereby you can choose to block receipt of cookies, to delete cookies, or to be prompted before cookies are received. Please note that, if you delete or choose not to receive cookies from our Sites, the functionality of the Sites may be impaired. Like many websites, our Sites use Google’s Analytics services, which involve the use of cookies to collect web traffic data.  Per the applicable service terms, Google Analytics does not collect personally identifiable information using such cookies, and Google’s use of data collected is subject to Google’s privacy policy.
Transactional Information
Information you provide is collected in connection with transactions, such as donations to the Museum, memberships, fundraisers, or purchases. This information includes your payment card information, billing address, phone number, and email address. We honor requests that donations be anonymous to the public, subject to any reporting obligations mandated by law.
Your payment card information will not be used for any purpose other than to process your transaction. Other personal information may be used to update the Museum’s records of donors and customers.
Third Party Service Providers
We sometimes provide personal information to third party vendors so that they may assist us in connection with ticket sales, event promotion, fundraising, or otherwise. However, we require that those providers provide assurances that they will appropriately protect personal information entrusted to them and use personal information only for that purpose.
All credit card transactions on the Sites are handled by trusted third parties. Our online store, ShopDMA.org, is hosted by Yahoo! Store (See Privacy Policy here). Online and box office ticketing are handled by Ticketleap (See Privacy Policy here). Online memberships and donations are facilitated by Springboard (See here).
Children’s Privacy
The Dallas Museum of Art is concerned about protecting children's privacy. Children under the age of 13 may not participate in the Friends program, and should not provide any information to us using the Sites.  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. The Dallas Museum of Art encourages all parents to participate in their children’s exploration of the Internet and to teach them about protecting their personal information while online. We urge those concerned or with questions to contact us for more information.
Contact Us
Your questions, comments and feedback are very important to us. For privacy-related issues, please contact the Director of Technology and Digital Media by phone on 214-922-1206, by email to webgroup@DMA.org, or by post addressed c/o Director of Technology and Digital Media, Dallas Museum of Art, 1717 North Harwood, Dallas, TX 75201.
Contact UsPressPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsCareersE-Mail Sign-upGive Now
VisitHours & DirectionsCalendarDiningMuseum StoreVisitor AccessibilityCenter for Creative ConnectionsHost an EventCOVID Safety Measures & FAQsNotice to Visitors About COVID-19ArtExhibitionsCollectionConservationTexas ArtDeaccessioned ArtworksWhat's NewProgramsAdult ProgramsFamily ProgramsClasses & WorkshopsArts & Letters LiveCommunity ProgramsTeen ProgramsAccess ProgramsSchool ProgramsResearchLibraryArchivesPublicationsProvenanceThe Edith O'Donnell Institute of Art HistoryVisitor Centered ResearchSupportMembershipCorporateInstitutional FundersFundraising EventsPlanned GivingVolunteerAnnual FundGive NowAboutDirector's WelcomeMission StatementMuseum HistoryEmploymentInternshipsAnnual ReportFinancialsBoard of TrusteesDirect Care of CollectionsEquity, Diversity and Inclusion PolicyAwards to ArtistsVirtual
The Dallas Museum of Art is supported, in part, by the generosity of DMA Members and donors, the citizens of Dallas through the City of Dallas Office of Cultural Affairs, and the Texas Commission on the Arts.
All contents © 2020 Dallas Museum of Art. All rights reserved. Please note that any use of content downloaded or printed from this site is limited to non-commercial personal or educational use, including “fair use” as defined by U.S. copyright laws.
